Guide to the Barbara Guest Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1953-2004; Series II
  - Writings by Guest
    - Drama
      - "Heart Attack: A Five Minute Drama", undated (Box 80, Folder 1436)
      - "Home Life of Poe", undated (Box 80, Folder 1437)
        1 handwritten
      - "The Lady's Choice", 1953 (Box 80, Folder 1438-1441)
        1 typescript (includes 2 bound versions); enclosures (note, program)
      - "The Office", undated (Box 81, Folder 1442-1444)
        1 typescript; enclosure (envelopes) [1 folder also contains "Often"]
      - "Often", 2000 (Box 81, Folder 1445)
        1 typescript; enclosure (program)
      - "Port", 1964–1984 July 21 (Box 81, Folder 1446-1448)
        1 typescript, corrected; enclosures (letter, program) [also contains "The Office"]
      - "Port" and "The Office", undated (Box 81, Folder 1449)
      - "Three Plays by Barbara Guest: Port, The Office, and Often", 2000 (Box 81, Folder 1450)
        Printed
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 81, Folder 1451)
    - Essays
      Other than notebooks, all essay drafts are typescripts
      - Notebooks #1-2, undated (Box 82, Folder 1452)
        Composite drafts
      - Notebooks #3, undated (Box 82, Folder 1453)
      - Notebook #4, undated (Box 82, Folder 1454)
      - Notebook #5, undated (Box 82, Folder 1455)
      - Notebook #7, undated (Box 82, Folder 1456)
        Composite drafts, includes essays and correspondence
      - Notebook #8, undated (Box 83, Folder 1457)
      - "Art in America: The Nineteen Fifties and Sixties", 1999 (Box 83, Folder 1458)
      - "Charles Bernstein: State of the Art", 1990 (Box 83, Folder 1459)
      - "Neil Blane at Yaddo in the 1950s", undated (Box 83, Folder 1460)
      - "The Color Green in the Art Work of Richard Tuttle", undated (Box 83, Folder 1461)
      - "Durer in the Window", undated (Box 83, Folder 1462-1465)
        Includes photographs and prined material submitted for publication
      - "An Evening with Charles Olson", 1999 November 20 (Box 83, Folder 1466)
        Includes letter from Guest to "Peter"
      - Essays on H.D., undated (Box 83, Folder 1467-1468)
      - "An Inconsiderate Preface", undated (Box 83, Folder 1469)
      - "Intimacy of Biography", undated (Box 83, Folder 1470)
      - "Invisible Architecture", undated (Box 84, Folder 1471-1474)
      - "Mysteriously Defining the Mysterious", undated (Box 84, Folder 1475-1476)
      - "On Jean Arp", undated (Box 84, Folder 1477)
      - "On Louis Bourgeois", undated (Box 84, Folder 1478)
      - "On Frank O'Hara", 2000 (Box 84, Folder 1479)
      - "On Leatrice Rose", undated (Box 84, Folder 1480)
      - "On James Schuyler", undated (Box 84, Folder 1481-1482)
      - "Poetry the True Fiction", undated (Box 84, Folder 1483)
      - "Prague Waking", undated (Box 84, Folder 1484)
      - "Leatrice Rose", undated (Box 84, Folder 1485)
      - "The Shadow of Surrealism", undated (Box 84, Folder 1486)
      - "The Vuillard of Us", undated (Box 84, Folder 1487)
      - Various essays, undated (Box 84, Folder 1488)
    - Herself Defined: The Poet H. D. and Her World
      - Correspondence regarding book, between Guest and various individuals, 1982–1983 (Box 85, Folder 1489-1491)
        Includes notes
      - Heydt, Erich, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 1492)
      - Verlag Press and Laurence Pollinger Lmtd., 1982 October 13–1983 December 13 (Box 85, Folder 1493)
      - Research notes and other materials, including copies of correspondence
        - H.D. and Richard Aldington, undated (Box 86, Folder 1494)
        - Allen, Frank, undated (Box 86, Folder 1495)
        - Cournos, John and H.D., undated (Box 86, Folder 1496)
        - d'Auria, Gemma, undated (Box 86, Folder 1497)
        - Dobson, Silvia, undated (Box 86, Folder 1498-1499)
        - Lowell, Amy, undated (Box 86, Folder 1500-1501)
        - Patmore, Brigit, undated (Box 87, Folder 1502)
        - Pearson, undated (Box 87, Folder 1503)
        - Pound, Ezra, undated (Box 87, Folder 1504)
        - Smyers, Virginia, undated (Box 87, Folder 1505-1506)
        - Williams, William Carlos, undated (Box 87, Folder 1507)
        - Various correspondents, undated (Box 87, Folder 1508-1509)
        - Index cards containing notes on individuals in H.D.'s books, undated (Box 88)
        - H.D. letters to Bryher, photocopies, undated (Box 89, Folder 1510-1511)
        - Research notes, undated (Box 90, Folder 1512-1524)
        - Research notes, undated (Box 91, Folder 1525-1530)
        - Photograph of book cover, undated (Box 91, Folder 1531)
        - Excerpts, undated (Box 91, Folder 1532-1533)
        - Research notes, undated (Box 92, Folder 1534-1539)
      - Drafts
        - Earliest draft, undated (Box 93, Folder 1540-1541)
        - First draft
          - Chapter 1, undated (Box 93, Folder 1542-1543)
          - Chapter 3, undated (Box 93, Folder 1544)
          - Chapter 5, undated (Box 93, Folder 1545)
          - Chapter 6, undated (Box 93, Folder 1546)
          - Chapter 9, undated (Box 93, Folder 1547)
          - Chapter 10, undated (Box 93, Folder 1548)
          - Chapters 10-12, undated (Box 93, Folder 1549)
          - Chapters 13-22 and 7-11, undated (Box 93, Folder 1550-1551)
          - Photographs for book, undated (Box 94, Folder 1552-1554)
        - Second draft
          - Chapters 1-4, undated (Box 95, Folder 1555)
          - Chapters 5-8, undated (Box 95, Folder 1556)
          - Chapters 13-18, undated (Box 95, Folder 1557)
          - Chapters 19-23, undated (Box 95, Folder 1558)
          - Chapter 24, undated (Box 95, Folder 1559)
          - Chapters 25-26, undated (Box 95, Folder 1560)
          - Chapters 27-29, undated (Box 95, Folder 1561)
        - Third draft, undated (Box 96, Folder 1562-1563)
        - Later drafts, undated (Box 96, Folder 1564-1566)
        - Later drafts, undated (Box 97, Folder 1567-1573)
        - Later drafts, undated (Box 98, Folder 1574-1578)
        - Later drafts, undated (Box 99, Folder 1579-1583)
      - Notes and draft excerpts, undated (Box 100, Folder 1584-1590)
      - Various photocopies of correspondence, undated (Box 101, Folder 1591)
      - Permissions, undated (Box 101, Folder 1592-1593)
      - "Sources", undated (Box 101, Folder 1594)
      - Acknowledgments, undated (Box 101, Folder 1595)
      - Bibliography, undated (Box 101, Folder 1596)
      - Proposal and reviewer and reader address lists, undated (Box 101, Folder 1597)
      - Book reviews and publicity, undated (Box 101, Folder 1598-1603)
        Includes correspondence with Laura Riding
      - Corrections, undated (Box 102, Folder 1604-1606)
      - Advance uncorrected proofs, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 1607)
      - Printed material and reviews, undated (Box 102, Folder 1608-1609)
    - Notes, undated
      - Various notes, undated (Box 170, Folder 1610-1614)
      - Various notes, undated (Box 106, Folder 1642-1650)
    - Lectures by Guest
      - "H.D. and the Conflict of Imagism." Barbara Guest at the Voice Box Royal Festival Hall, London, 1992 April 26 (Box 105, Folder 1632)
      - "A Talk on 'Startling Maneuvers'" in Poetry Project (printed version), December/January 1998/1989 (Box 105, Folder 1633)
      - Other lectures, undated (Box 105, Folder 1634-1641)
    - Other writings, undated
      - Reviews by Guest, undated (Box 104, Folder 1618-1631)
      - Reviews by Guest, undated (Box 103, Folder 1615-1617)
      - Bibliography, undated (Box 166, Folder 2153-2157)
  - Writings by others
    Writings by others contains writing drafts of others that various writers shared with Guest. Most notable among the subseries are writings by Mei-Mei Berssenbrugge and Sara Lundquist. Many of the writings are on Guest and her writing. Guest organized essays about herself together and these folders are filed at the end of the subseries.
    Also in the subseries are reviews on works by Guest and interview with Guest.
    - "A.B." "Pour Barbara", undated (Box 107, Folder 1651)
      Autograph manuscript
    - Anderson, Beth. "Imperturbable Things: On Still-Life Poetics", 1997 June (Box 107, Folder 1652)
      Booklet, from "The Impercipient Lecture Series, vol. 1 no. 5"
    - Antin, David. "Definitions", 1967 (Box 107, Folder 1653)
      Printed in notebook
    - Ed. Ballerini, Luigi, et al. "Italian Poetry After 1975", 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1654)
      Printed (spiral-bound)
    - Beilharz, Johannes. Translations of Barbara Guest's poetry into German, 2001 December 18–2002 March 24 (Box 107, Folder 1655)
      1 typescript and bound; enclosures (email correspondence)
    - Berssenbrugge, Mei-Mei. "Empathy", undated (Box 107, Folder 1656)
      1 typescript; enclosures (note to Guest, some poems possibly unrelated)
    - Berssenbrugge, Mei-Mei. "Fragrance", undated (Box 107, Folder 1657)
      1 typescript; enclosure (Berssenbrugge's bio with notes by Berssenbrugge and Guest)
    - Berssenbrugge, Mei-Mei. "The Heat Bird", undated (Box 107, Folder 1658)
      1 typescript; enclosure (typescript letter from Berssenbrugge to Guest)
    - Berssenbrugge, Mei-Mei. "The Peacock", undated (Box 107, Folder 1659)
      1 typescript with handwritten note by Berssenbrugge
    - Berssenbrugge, Mei-Mei. "Susie, Kiki, Annie", 1998 May 25 (Box 107, Folder 1660)
      1 typescript; enclosure (letter from Berssenbrugge to Guest)
    - Berssenbrugge, Mei-Mei. [Untitled collection of poems], undated (Box 107, Folder 1661)
      1 typescript; enclosure (note from Berssenbrugge to Guest)
    - Berssenbrugge, Mei-Mei. [Untitled collection of poems], 1995 November 13 (Box 107, Folder 1662)
    - Berssenbrugge, Mei-Mei. [Untitled collection of poems], undated (Box 108, Folder 1663)
      1 typescript with numerous edits and autograph manuscript notes; enclosures (many letters from Berssenbrugge to Guest)
    - Caples, Garrett. "The Barbara Guest Experience", undated (Box 108, Folder 1664-1665)
      1 typescript; enclosures (emails from Guest to Caples in one folder)
    - Cole, Norma. "Spinoza in Her Youth", 1999 February 15 (Box 108, Folder 1666)
      Photocopy of magazine; enclosures ("Minutes of the Charles Olson Society" by Guest, letter from Peter Quartermain to Guest, postcard from Garrett [Caples] to Guest)
    - Dash, Robert. "A Few Things About Several Important Paintings", undated (Box 108, Folder 1667)
      Typescript, corrected, poems
    - DuPlessis, Rachel Blau. "The Flavor of Eyes", 1995 October (Box 108, Folder 1668)
      Copy of magazine; enclosures (letter from DuPlessis to Guest, essay "The Gendered Marvelous" by DuPlessis)
    - Elmslie, Kenward. Various poems, undated (Box 108, Folder 1669)
      Typescript
    - Equi, Elaine. "Following Barbara Guest in a Dream", undated (Box 108, Folder 1670)
      1 typescript; enclosure (photograph)
    - F[erlinghetti], Lawrence. Untitled, undated (Box 108, Folder 1671)
      Drawing by Ferlinghetti; poems apparently by Guest
    - Fraser, Kathleen. "Notes Preceding Trust", 1987 (Box 108, Folder 1672)
    - Fraser, Kathleen. "This Phrasing Unreliable Except As Here", 1993 November 2 (Box 108, Folder 1673)
    - Fraser, Kathleen. "One Hundred and Three Chapters of Little Times: Collapsed and Transfigured Moments in the Fiction of Barbara Guest", undated (Box 108, Folder 1674)
      1 typescript and photocopy of printed version
    - Gevirtz, Susan. "Dwarf of Passage", undated (Box 108, Folder 1675)
      1 typescript and enclosure (printed booklet "Spelt" by Gevirtz and Myung Mi Kim)
    - Gevirtz, Susan. "Hourglass Transcripts", 2001 (Box 108, Folder 1676)
      Printed book; enclosures (typescript poems) [seems to be the same as "Dwarf of Passage" above]
    - Gevirtz, Susan. "Thrall: Chapter Book", undated (Box 108, Folder 1677)
    - Graffi, Milli. "Lo schermo della distanza", undated (Box 108, Folder 1678)
      1 typescript [Italian translation of a poem by Guest]
    - Holub, Miroslav. Untitled selection of poems, undated (Box 109, Folder 1679)
    - Howe, Susan. "Defenestration of Prague", undated (Box 109, Folder 1680)
    - Joseph, René. "Lifting the Veil of Sight: The Paintings and Teachings of Mary Abbott", 1996 (Box 109, Folder 1681)
    - Kaufman, Robert. [Three essays], undated (Box 109, Folder 1682)
      1 typescript; enclosures (letter from Kaufman to Guest) [essay titles are "The End of Negative Capability, Coda from Barbara Guest"; "The Future of Modernism: Barbara Guest's Recent Poetry"; "Adorno's Lyric Poetry, with Two Experiments by Michael Palmer"]
    - Keller, Lynn. "Becoming 'a Compleat Travel Agency': Barbara Guest's Negotiations with the '50s Feminine Mystique", undated (Box 109, Folder 1683)
      1 typescript; enclosures (letter from Keller to Guest, some fliers)
    - Killian, Kevin, and Barbara Guest. "Often", 2001 July (Box 109, Folder 1684)
      Printed booklet; enclosures (webpage for the play, correspondence between Guest and Killian)
    - Lundquist, Sara. "Another Poet Among Painters: Barbara Guest, Grace Hartigan, Mary Abbott", undated (Box 109, Folder 1685)
      3 typescript copies; enclosures (note and letter from Lundquist to Guest)
    - Lundquist, Sara. "Barbara Guest", 1997 October 10 (Box 109, Folder 1686-1687)
      3 typescript copies; enclosures (fliers, note from Nicholas [?] to Guest)
    - Lundquist, Sara. "Barbara Guest's Stripped Tales: Narrative Echoes and Erasures", 1999 April (Box 109, Folder 1688)
    - Lundquist, Sara. "The Fifth Point of a Star: Barbara Guest and the New York School of Poets", undated (Box 109, Folder 1689)
    - Lundquist, Sara. "Implacable Poet, Purple Birds: the Work of Barbara Guest", undated (Box 109, Folder 1690)
      1 typescript; enclosures (letter from Lundquist to Guest, several unrelated typescript pages, printed booklet "El Templo" by Cecilia Vicuña)
    - Matthews, Harry. Poems, undated (Box 109, Folder 1691)
    - O'Hara, Frank. "The Houses at Falling Hanging", undated (Box 109, Folder 1692)
      Photocopies made from microfilm
    - Retallack, Joan. "The Blue Stares", undated (Box 109, Folder 1693)
      1 typescript, includes letter to Guest from R.
    - Robinson, Elizabeth. [Untitled selection of poems], undated (Box 109, Folder 1694)
    - Rosselli, Amelia. "From 'Forum Italicum'", undated (Box 109, Folder 1695)
      Copy of printed book
    - Saidenberg, Joyce. "CUSP", undated (Box 109, Folder 1696)
    - Schultz, Susan. "'Called Null or Called Vocative': A Fate of the Contemporary Lyric", undated (Box 109, Folder 1697)
    - Schuyler, Jimmy. Poetry, undated (Box 109, Folder 1698)
    - Slacik, Anne. "Les jardins, œuvres sur papier, livres et manuscrits peints", 1999 (Box 109, Folder 1699)
      Printed booklet; enclosures (fliers)
    - Taylor, Julene C. "Barbara Guest's Poetic Journey", 1996- (Box 110, Folder 1700)
    - Vicuña, Cecilia. "Instan", 2002 June 23 (Box 110, Folder 1701)
      Proof
    - Waldman, Anne. "After Li Ching Chao", 1983 (Box 110, Folder 1702)
      Printed with autograph manuscript note
    - Waldrop, Rosmarie. "The Reproduction of Profiles", 1987 (Box 110, Folder 1703)
    - Welish, Marjorie. "The Annotated 'Here'", undated (Box 110, Folder 1704)
      1 typescript (spiral bound)
    - Welish, Marjorie. "The Windows Flew Open", undated (Box 110, Folder 1705)
      Copy of printed book; enclosure (note from Welish to Guest)
    - Welish, Marjorie. [Untitled selection of poems], undated (Box 110, Folder 1706)
    - Welish, Marjorie. "Casting Sequences", undated (Box 110, Folder 1707)
      1 typescript, bound
    - Wheeler, Susan. "Bag o' Diamonds", 1994 (Box 110, Folder 1708)
      Proofs; enclosure (letter from Elaine Dasher to Guest)
    - Wilkinson, Louis. "Swan's Milk" and "The Buffoon", undated (Box 110, Folder 1709)
    - Yau, John. Poems, 1978 July 21 (Box 110, Folder 1710)
    - Various authors. Essays on Guest, undated (Box 110, Folder 1711-1713)
      1 typescript [both folders contain identical material]
    - Reviews on works by Guest, undated (Box 111, Folder 1714-1720)
    - Interviews with Guest, undated (Box 112, Folder 1721-1727)
- Personal Papers, 1943-2006; Series III
  Organized into three subseries: Dayplanners and calendars, Diaries and notebooks, and Other papers
  Personal Papers includes dayplanners, calendars, diaries, and notebooks kept by Guest. They are all dated. Other papers include material relating to Guest's death and funeral and services, such as writings on Guest that were shared during her memorial service, the guest book for her funeral, and various printed obituaries. Also present is material collected by Guest relating to her family's history and genealogy.
  - Dayplanners and calendars
    Arranged chronologically. An undated dayplanner is filed at the end of the subseries.
    - 1953 (Box 113, Folder 1728)
    - 1955 (Box 113, Folder 1729)
    - 1956 (Box 113, Folder 1730)
    - 1957 (Box 113, Folder 1731)
    - 1958 (Box 113, Folder 1732)
    - 1959 (Box 113, Folder 1733)
    - 1960 (Box 113, Folder 1734)
    - 1961 (Box 114, Folder 1735)
    - 1962 (Box 114, Folder 1736)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 114, Folder 1737)
    - 1964 (Box 114, Folder 1738)
    - 1965 (Box 114, Folder 1739)
    - 1966 (Box 114, Folder 1740)
    - 1967 (Box 115, Folder 1741)
    - 1968 (Box 115, Folder 1742)
    - 1969 (Box 115, Folder 1743)
    - 1970 (Box 115, Folder 1744)
    - 1971 (Box 115, Folder 1745)
    - 1972 (Box 115, Folder 1746)
    - 1973 (Box 115, Folder 1747)
    - 1974 (Box 115, Folder 1748)
    - 1975 (Box 116, Folder 1749)
    - 1976 (Box 116, Folder 1750)
    - 1977 (Box 116, Folder 1751)
    - 1978 (Box 116, Folder 1752)
    - 1980 (Box 116, Folder 1753)
    - 1984 (Box 116, Folder 1754)
    - 1986 (Box 116, Folder 1755)
    - 1987 (Box 116, Folder 1756)
    - 1988 (Box 116, Folder 1757)
    - 1989 (Box 117, Folder 1758)
    - 1990 (Box 117, Folder 1759)
    - 1991 (Box 117, Folder 1760)
    - 1991 (Box 117, Folder 1761)
    - 1992 (Box 117, Folder 1762)
    - 1993 (Box 117, Folder 1763)
    - 1994 (Box 117, Folder 1764)
    - 1996 (Box 117, Folder 1765)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 117, Folder 1766)
    - 1998 (Box 118, Folder 1767)
    - 1999 (Box 118, Folder 1768)
    - 2000 (Box 118, Folder 1769)
    - 2001 (Box 118, Folder 1770)
    - undated (Box 119, Folder 1771)
  - Diaries and notebooks
    - Empty envelopes, undated (Box 120, Folder 1772)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 120, Folder 1773)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 120, Folder 1774)
    - 1991 (Box 120, Folder 1775)
    - Various dates (Box 120, Folder 1776)
    - Various dates (Box 120, Folder 1777)
    - 1993-2000 (Box 121, Folder 1778)
    - 1997-1999 (Box 121, Folder 1779)
    - "The Kingdom of the Pool", undated (Box 121, Folder 1780-1782)
    - Atlases of Los Angeles City and County, 1943 and 1962 (Box 121, Folder 1783)
  - Other papers
    - Barbara Guest Funeral, Memorial Service, and Tributes, 2006
      - Printed materials, undated (Box 122, Folder 1784)
        Includes service programs
      - Writings by others on Guest, including Peter Gizzi's piece on Barbara Guest in the Journal of the Academy of American Poets, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 1785-1786)
      - Guest book for Barbara Guest's funeral, 2006 February 24 (Box 122, Folder 1787)
      - Printed obituaries, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 1788)
    - Family Material, undated
      - ITT Hartford account statement and printed material, 1996 (Box 123, Folder 1789)
      - "Family material", 1950–1999 (Box 123, Folder 1790)
        Includes photographs, letters, and obituaries
      - "Barbara Guest, born Barbara Ann Pinson, 1920 September 6; Family history - Pinsons/Tabors, undated (Box 123, Folder 1791)
        Includes photographs of old photographs, letters, obituaries
      - "Recent family histry of Barbara Guest: Born Barbara Ann Pinson, 1920 in Wilmington, North Carolina, 2005 September 12 (Box 123, Folder 1792)
      - "Barbara Guest Geneology", 2002 (Box 123, Folder 1793)
        Photocopies of correspondence and other family material
- Professional Papers, circa 1950-2006; Series IV
  This series includes groupings of material prepared by Guest, including printed material, correspondence, writings drafts, and other papers relating to Guest's professional life.
  - Unsorted papers arranged into folders by Guest, undated (Box 167, Folder 1810-1816)
  - Unsorted papers arranged into folders by Guest, undated (Box 168, Folder 1823-1829)
  - Unsorted papers arranged into folders by Guest, undated (Box 169, Folder 1834-1845)
  - Unsorted papers arranged into folders by Guest, undated (Box 127, Folder 1846-1854)
  - Unsorted papers arranged into folders by Guest, undated (Box 128, Folder 1855-1861)
  - Unsorted papers arranged into folders by Guest, undated (Box 129, Folder 1862-1866)
  - Unsorted papers arranged into folders by Guest, undated (Box 130, Folder 1867-1872)
  - Unsorted papers arranged into folders by Guest, undated (Box 131, Folder 1873-1880)
  - Typewriter (Box 171)
- Photographs, circa 1923-2004; Series V
  This series is organized into four subseries: Photographs of Guest and others, Portraits, Photograph albums, and "Photographs A-Z".
  Photographs of Guest contains photographs of Guest, her immediate and extended family, friends, colleagues, and other individuals. Portraits are primarily of Guest but portraits of others are present. Photograph albums are of family and friends, Guest's celebration of her Festschrfit at Bonn University, and a photograph album of Guest's plays being performed. "Photographs A-Z" contains photographs foldered and arranged alphebtically by Guest. These photographs depict Guest, her family, friends and landscapes.
  - Photographs of Guest and others
    This subseries was arranged according to how photographs were grouped together upon acquisition.
    - Barbara Guest, Bob Fabian, and Fay Lousner, circa 1988 (Box 132, Folder 1881)
    - Hadley Guest, 1991 (Box 132, Folder 1882)
    - Guest in front of Louvre, 1968 (Box 132, Folder 1883)
    - Jonathan Higgins in Olympia, Greece, 1965 (Box 132, Folder 1884)
    - Family, 1958 (Box 132, Folder 1885)
    - Guest on ship, the New Amsterdam, to Europe, 1965 (Box 132, Folder 1886)
    - Hadley Guest by Karen Hagen Liste, circa 1965 (Box 132, Folder 1887)
    - Barbara Guest with Ilse Getz, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 1888)
    - Hadley Haden-Guest, Jonathan Higgins, and acquaintance on ship, circa 1961 (Box 132, Folder 1889)
    - Guest with Hadley and Jonathan, 1960 (Box 132, Folder 1890)
    - Greece, 1965 (Box 132, Folder 1891)
    - Guest's great-great grandmother, undated (Box 132, Folder 1892)
    - Guest's grandmother, undated (Box 132, Folder 1893)
    - Various family, undated (Box 132, Folder 1894)
    - "Life in Southampton, NY", undated (Box 132, Folder 1895)
    - Guest in Southampton, circa 1970 (Box 132, Folder 1896)
    - H.D., undated (Box 132, Folder 1897)
    - Hadley Haden-Guest, undated (Box 132, Folder 1898)
    - Guest by Chris Felver, undated (Box 132, Folder 1899)
    - Various photographs of interiors and John Edwards presidential campaign, undated (Box 132, Folder 1900)
    - Photographs of Guest and "Moscow Mansions", undated (Box 132, Folder 1901)
    - Guest by Gloria Graham, 2003 (Box 133, Folder 1902)
    - Young Guest, circa 1923 (Box 133, Folder 1903)
    - Photos sent by Carolyn Harris, undated (Box 133, Folder 1904)
      Includes letter
    - Guest at Yaddo with others, undated (Box 133, Folder 1905)
    - Guest and family, 1951 (Box 133, Folder 1906)
    - Various photographs of interiors and John Edwards presidential campaign, 1950–2004 (Box 133, Folder 1907)
    - Photographs of family, 1983 (Box 133, Folder 1908)
    - Guest with friends, 1990s (Box 133, Folder 1909)
    - Photographs of family, undated (Box 133, Folder 1910)
    - Photographs of family, undated (Box 133, Folder 1911)
    - Photographs and slides of paintings, undated (Box 133, Folder 1912)
    - Central Park, 1950s (Box 133, Folder 1913)